http://www.sojo.net/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
By using sojo.net you agree to our Privacy Policy
faith in action for social justice
AboutAbout SojournersFounder Jim WallisOur TeamMediaWays to GiveWork With UsContact Us
SojoActionOverviewTake ActionEventsResourcesFaith-Rooted AdvocatesChurch Engagement
MagazineCurrent IssueArchivesWrite for Sojourners
SectionsLatestElection 2020PoliticsColumnsLiving FaithArts & CultureGlobalPodcastsVideoPreaching The Word
Privacy Policy
Sojourners is committed to preserving your privacy and safeguarding your information. Your email address is never sold or shared beyond our own platforms. The following statements describe our general information-gathering and usage practices:
Subscriptions
Magazine Subscriptions
Personal identifying information (data about you) is collected when you subscribe, through the webpages hosted on our site. These webpages are hosted for Sojourners by our Circulation Service Provider, Cambey & West Inc.
This Personal identifying information (PII) includes your name, email address, and phone number that you provided. You will have also provided a credit card to pay for your subscription, and while needed for processing your payment, the card number is not stored. Instead the transaction id received back from the card processor is stored. All of the PII data is stored within the Cambey & West system, which has been tested and verified to be PCI compliant as a Level 1 Service Provider by an independent agency. This is a thorough and rigorous testing of the security, proving the inability to penetrate and acquire any data stored within it.
When you submitted a subscription form hosted on our site, you entered into an agreement with us to provide you the subscription you requested in exchange for PII and the subscription fees. Your data will not be shared with any third parties without your express consent.Your PII is retained for the duration of your subscription.
Since this is your data, at any point you have the right to:
access and review your data
correct your data
withdraw your consent
be forgotten, erasure of your data.
You can manage your subscription by logging in and going here or contact sojourners@sojo.net / 202.328.8842 to request changes to your account. Requests will be addressed in 30 days or less.
Preaching the Word Subscriptions
To ensure access to the Preaching the Word section of the website, we ask subscribers to create a user account, which requires collecting an email. Preaching the Word subscriptions are securely processed by our contracted vendor Recurly. See Recurly's Privacy Policy here.
Website
E-mail Lists
Sojourners uses Blackbaud's Luminate program to manage emails gathered on the website. Read about Blackbaud's General Data Protection Regulation compliance here.
We ask for data, such as zip codes, so that we can send you the most relevant event announcements or opportunities for action. Sojourners will not sell, trade, or give away email addresses that are subscribed to our email lists — such as SojoMail, our weekly email newsletter — to any other organization or entity without your consent.
User Accounts
When a visitor registers for a user account on our website — to access the magazine or Preaching the Word content — we collect the user's email address to communicate any updates. Mange your user account here.
Cookies
This website uses browser cookies to enhance your user experience and store display preferences.  We do not collect or store any personally identifying data and we certainly don't share or sell data collected in this manner.
Google Analytics
Sojourners uses Google Analytics to better understand our audience by anonymously tracking which pieces are the most read and most engaging, where our visitors come to us from, and to drive our strategy.
Donor Privacy Policy
As a 501(c)(3) nonprofit, we rely on the generous contributions of our supporters. We value the faithful support of our financial community and therefore take the privacy of our donors very seriously.
Out of mutual respect we will not rent, sell, or exchange any personal donor information with outside parties, organizations, or individuals. This includes all relevant information obtained through online donation forms, dispatched appeals, phone calls, and in person solicitation. Online credit card donations are processed securely by our contracted e-commerce service. We maintain this information in our database in order to keep you up-to-date on our future work and related issues that may be of interest. If you wish to refrain from receiving our emails and/or direct mail solicitation, you can contact our office at donate@sojo.net or call 202-328-8842.
If you have further questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at sojourners@sojo.net or call 202-328-8842.
Search Sojourners
×
Search
X for more info
